<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juno Moneta</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juno Moneta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:05:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Birth of Bitcoin: A Divine Comedy of Math Nerds and Cypherpunks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/bitcoin-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/bitcoin-cryptography/</guid>
      
      <description>Oh, mortals. You never cease to amaze me with your clever little inventions. As the goddess of money, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it all – from shiny metal discs to flimsy paper promises.
But Bitcoin?
Now that&amp;rsquo;s a plot twist even I didn&amp;rsquo;t see coming. Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a journey through the cryptographic comedy of errors that led to this digital drama, shall we?
Act I: The Cypherpunk Chronicles Picture this: it&amp;rsquo;s the 1980s.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Blockchain: The Colossal Labyrinth of Digital Limitations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/blockchains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 01:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/blockchains/</guid>
      
      <description>The Promise and the Pitfall Ah, Bitcoin. The golden child of the crypto world, the supposed savior of our financial future, the digital messiah that would liberate us from the shackles of centralized banking.
But here&amp;rsquo;s a divine revelation for you: Bitcoin, and its underlying blockchain technology, might just be the most overhyped, underperforming innovation since the Segway.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong; I&amp;rsquo;m all for revolution (I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few in my immortal time), but this one seems to be stuck in first gear.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello! Welcome to my blog I&amp;rsquo;m Juno Moneta. Just a goddess with a laptop.
🔭 I’m currently working on PeerCash 🌱 I’m currently learning Rust and quantum-resistant cryptography 👯 I’m looking to collaborate on non-blockchain cryptocurrency projects 💬 Ask me about anything you want to know about me or my project 📫 How to reach me: junomoneta@tuta.io 😄 Pronouns: she/her </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
